xprt.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy | Advertise on XPRT

So that you can better protect your privacy, XPRT Media provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used. If you do not agree with the practices explained in this policy, do not complete the User Registration form.

Note: Without registering, you cannot access certain features of XPRT Media sites

## **Personal Information**

At times, XPRT Media sites will ask you to provide us with personal contact information. We will use this information to help customize your site experience or to facilitate communication with the companies listed on our site. You will be prompted to supply us with this information when signing up to use XPRT user features or when initiating communication through the site.

## **What Information Do We Collect**

**a) Personal Data:** As stated before, you are not required to provide information directly to us in order to view the Site. However, when you use certain Site functions, such as when you register for certain services, access certain content or features, or directly contact the Site or suppliers listed in it, we may ask you to provide information, including:

  * contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, and mobile number;
  * username and password;
  * information posted in community discussions and other interactive online features;
  * search queries conducted on the Site; and
  * correspondence you send to us.

**b) Usage Data:**

When you visit and interact with the Site, certain information may be collected automatically, including:

  * your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address;
  * your browser type and operating system;
  * the web pages you were visiting immediately before and after you came to the Site;
  * web pages and advertisements that you view, and links that you click on, within the Site;
  * aggregated data about email click-through rates and user video viewing;
  * standard server log information; and
  * information collected through HTML cookies, Flash cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies.

**c) Information we collect from other sources:**

We may access information about you from third-party sources and platforms (such as social networking sites, databases, online marketing firms, and ad targeting firms), including:

  * if you access third-party social networking services (such as Facebook Connect or Twitter) through the Site, your username and connection lists for those services;
  * demographic data, such as age range, gender, and interests;
  * advertisement interaction and viewing data, such as ad click-through rates and information about how many times you viewed a particular ad; and

Please note that the Site may combine the information that we collect with information we obtain from third-party sources.

## **User Registration**

While you do not need to sign up to use XPRT Media sites, we do need some information from you to access certain features of the site; you are asked for limited personal and demographic information and are required to choose a username and password that will be used to gain access on subsequent visits to XPRT Media sites. This information will constitute your user profile. While most of the information we collect is used internally for site analysis and improvement, some of your information is used in compiling reports (see the Reporting section below) for the companies listed on our site.

By creating an account you agree to receive notifications from us regarding your account or services provided by XPRT Media. These notifications could come in the form of emails, banners or alerts on XPRT Media’s online properties.

You may edit or change your profile at any time by logging in.

## **Communicating With Suppliers**

When you use the communication features on XPRT Media sites to contact suppliers, you will be asked to supply the contact information required by these companies to respond to your request. Depending on how you wish the company to respond to your request, you may be asked for the following: telephone number; mailing address and e-mail.

If you have not registered as a user, we will not store any of the contact information you enter unless you choose to register with us.

XPRT Media users will be able to verify or change the information stored in their profile prior to sending the request.

Many of the suppliers listed on XPRT Media sites will make additional information, such as brochures, videos, articles, web links, etc. available to the users of XPRT Media sites free of charge. Some of these suppliers may require your contact information in exchange for access to this information. By providing your personal details in order to gain access to this information you are granting permission to the supplier to make use of your personal data to contact you regarding the products and services they provide. Please note once your personal data has been shared with the supplier, it is out of the control of XPRT Media and you may need to contact the supplier directly to exercise your privacy rights.

## **E-mail Communications Policy**

By signing up with XPRT Media sites and providing us with your e-mail address you agree to accept essential communication concerning the services and operation of XPRT Media including, but not limited to: confirmation, additions or deletions to our core services, notifications of product enhancements, notification of service interruption and changes to this policy.

As part of the sign up process, and at any time thereafter, you have the opportunity to opt in to receive non-essential communication, including newsletters and announcements, from XPRT Media and third parties via e-mail by checking the appropriate boxes on the User Registration form.

All e-mail communications from XPRT Media or from third parties wishing to contact our users are sent by XPRT Media or a provider under contract to XPRT Media. At no time will we ever distribute your e-mail address to another company except as stated in the “Communicating with Suppliers” section of this notice.

All non-essential communications from XPRT Media will contain a link or instructions for opting out of future communications.

## **Cookies**

XPRT Media sites may set cookies on your computer.

A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by our web server. Cookies are uniquely generated and assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the same domain that set the cookie on your computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

The primary purposes of cookies used by XPRT Media are to provide convenience and to save you time. XPRT Media will use cookies to automate login, enable personalization, facilitate your movement through the site and allow us to measure site usage.

## **Logging**

XPRT Media makes extensive use of web logging to understand the usage of our services, diagnose problems and identify future enhancements to our site. In addition to logging the pages viewed, and features used, our logs will also collect referring IP addresses or domain names of site visitors. This information is used in the reporting and analysis of our website, some of which will be shared with XPRT Media vendors and clients.

## **Reporting**

XPRT Media sites is offered for free on the Internet as a direct result of the paid support of the suppliers who provide information and advertise on our site. As a result we provide these suppliers with reports of non-specific information on the usage of XPRT Media sites collected from our logs or non-personal information provided during the sign up process. This reporting can be based on any of the information collected by XPRT Media and can include demographic information (industry, job function, and city) and your company name.

## **Data Security**

XPRT Media uses reasonable precautions to keep user information disclosed to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

XPRT Media will disclose such information to third parties, under contract to us, as required to operate our site. We will only release this information to those firms that we believe to be responsible. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties who receive the information.

XPRT Media sites also links to a wide variety of other web sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they collect or treat information about their users.

## **Transfer of Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## **General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

We may process your Personal Data because:

a)     We need to perform a contract with you  
b)     You have given us permission to do so  
c)     The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights  
d)     For payment processing purposes  
e)     To comply with the law

We are committed to helping you exercise your rights under the GDPR, which include:

**Transparency and the right of information.** This page explains what data we collect from you and how it is used. If you have any concerns, you can always contact us.

**Right of access, objection, restriction of processing, erasure, and portability.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time when we process your personal data based on your consent. To exercise these rights, please contact us at support@xprt.com.

**Right to opt-out to direct marketing.** You have the right to opt-out at any time to receiving marketing materials from us by following the opt-out instructions in our commercial emails, by contacting us, or by adjusting your preferences under your Profile Settings on the Site.

Please note that we reserve the right to send you other communications, including service announcements and administrative messages relating to your XPRT Media account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. You can always have your account deleted permanently from our records by contacting us.

**Right not to be subject to an automated decision, including profiling.** We do not make automated decisions using your personal data that may negatively impact you. We use cookies and similar technologies on our Site to personalize your experience on the Site and recommending content that may be of interest to you.

**Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.** If you consider that the processing of your personal data infringes your privacy rights according to the European Data Protection law, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in the member state of your habitual residence, place of work, or place of the alleged infringement.

## **Changes to this Policy**

XPRT Media reserves the right to change this policy as required. Users who have signed up to use XPRT Media sites will be notified of significant changes using the e-mail of record in their user profile. Users who have not signed up should review this policy periodically or prior to any subsequent use.

If you have any questions regarding this policy or wish to be removed from our database please contact us at support@xprt.com
